coms.hk 2018-03-16

# Privacy Policy - coms.hk Free Domain Name Service | Stability and security domain name that belongs to Hongkonger

This privacy policy is about our practices regarding data collection and use from all of our services.

## Information we collect

We collect non-personal information to give you a fabulous user experience on our website. These non-personal information may include IP address, date/time, browser type, operating system, referring page and clickstream data. When you sign up an account on our website, we will collect your personal information. These personal information may include your name, email address and telephone number.

## How we use information we collect

We use the information we collect to provide, maintain, improve, protect and develop our services. Infomation will automatically collected and stored in server logs and third-party software. We may also use cookies (e.g. PHP session cookies), browser web storage and application data caches to assist in collecting and storing information.

## Updating your information

Unless we have to keep the information for system processing and legal purposes, you may review, delete inaccuracies and update personal information through our website. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we act on your request. We may reject requests that are unreasonable, require disproportionate technical effort, or risk the privacy of others. After you update infomation through our website, we may not immediately update residual copies from our active servers and our backup systems.

## Information we share

Generally, only some of your infomation will show on our WHOIS page due to the disclosure of the domain name owner. Otherwise, we will not disclose your information to third-party unless it is for legal purposes.

## Changes

Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If the changes are significant, we will notify you either posting a notice or by emailing affected individuals.

(Last Updated: 2014-03-31)
